{
    "id": "0d490d3da4e04388801a95e82f68b968",
    "title": "Early or Soon | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t like to get up ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "soon",
                "early"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea09218366be4a509775df2d8873acdf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bye Charlie, see you ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd8f046e8b8e4100af1aa162c0552fa3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie left her office at 6 o’clock, so she should be here ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "soon",
                "early"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ae2d9c4a8f8456c9de62e42178990f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government is expected to announce revised tax policies ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bde7d15896704b56b3d59a7de65cfbab"
        },
        {
            "question": "I arrived …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6b042b972a7436781b31e204ac02d05"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you finish this job as ………………. as possible?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d71e5d863ed441799273d26492a5ca0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is in her ………………. twenties.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8522ccae6980433a9cf0ff2ff868bcc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents immigrated to Canada in the ..................... 1980s.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f75fc162ebaa43f985f5a00936805f32"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at the sky. It is going to rain ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ce44609245a4a0d845685fe3f43661a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Get well ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd79727d86e041d58d4b5d90000a314b"
        }
    ]
}